Announcer:
PREVIOUSLY IN TEEN HORROR FILMS...
[TELEPHONE SPEED DIALS]
Telephone: HELLO,
AND WELCOME TO MOVIEFONE.
IF YOU KNOW THE NAME OF
THE MOVIE YOU'D LIKE TO SEE,
PRESS ONE.
TO CHOOSE FROM A LIST
OF CURRENT, OVER-PRICED
BLOOD-SPLATTERED
BLOCKBUSTERS,
PRESS 2.
FOR CHICK FLICKS
WITH A GAY BEST FRIEND,
PRESS 3.
FOR BIG STUDIO BOMBS...
[TELEPHONE BEEPS]
PRESS 4.
FOR POLITICALLY CORRECT
BUDDY MOVIES,
PRESS 5.
DAD?
[DISTORTED VOICE]
HELLO, SYDNEY.
THIS ISN'T CINDY.
I THINK YOU HAVE
THE WRONG NUMBER.
UH, WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT NUMBER DID I DIAL?
WHO IS THIS?
[SHOES SQUEAK]
THE KILLER.
[TELEPHONE BEEPS]
IS THAT YOURS OR MINE?
IGNORE IT.
I HAVE VOICE MAIL.
DO YOU LIKE MOVIES?
YEAH, SURE.
I RENTED SOME TONIGHT.
WHAT KIND OF MOVIES?
OH, THE USUAL:
VASELINE ALLEY;
TWO GUYS, A GIRL,
AND A HORSE;
A BIG BLACK...
I GET IT! I GET IT!
ANYWAY, DO YOU LIKE
SCARY MOVIES?
OH, YOU MEAN LIKE
SPIKE LEE MOVIES?
LOOK. LAY OFF THE SPIKESTER.
HE'S KEEPIN' IT REAL.
LET'S PLAY A GAME.
DO YOU LIKE GAMES?
I GUESS.
ALL RIGHT.
A TRAIN LEAVES CHICAGO
DOING 60 MILES AN HOUR...
MATH? HOW AM I
SUPPOSED TO KNOW THAT?
I'M A BEAUTIFUL,
POPULAR RICH KID
WITH A PROMISING FUTURE
IN A LIGHTWEIGHT SORORITY
AT A STATE COLLEGE.
I DON'T NEED
TO KNOW THAT STUFF.
I'M GONNA GET MARRIED.
SHUT UP!
SHUT UP, YOU NITWIT.
DO YOU THINK THIS
STALKING THING IS EASY?
WHOA!
[SPLASH]
ARE YOU IN MY POOL?
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
[RING]
HELLO?
Operator:
COLLECT CALL FROM...
Killer: THE KILLER.
WILL YOU
ACCEPT THE CHARGES?
WHATEVER.
GO AHEAD.
THANKS.
NOW, WHERE WERE WE?
NOW, LOOK, GEEK.
NO. YOU LOOK.
IF YOU DON'T GET
THIS NEXT QUESTION RIGHT,
YOU'RE DEAD MEAT.
WHO'S BURIED
IN GRANT'S TOMB?
UH, HUGH GRANT.
I'M AFRAID NOT, GENIUS.
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
OH! IT WAS AMY GRANT,
WASN'T IT?
I WAS GONNA SAY THAT.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
YOU DIDN'T ANSWER
IN THE FORM OF A QUESTION.
[BLADE UNSHEATHES]
HEY, YOU'RE NOT
MARILYN MELONS.
WHOA!
OOF!
[SHOES SQUEAKING]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
HELLO?
YEAH,
HOLD ON A MINUTE.
IT'S STACY.
HI. DO YOU MIND?
[SHOES SQUEAK]
NOTHING.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT DID SHE SAY?
SHE IS SUCH A BITCH.
LOOK. I GOT TO GO.
I'LL CALL YOU BACK.
OOH! OH!
DAMN THAT NOSE.
I'M MELTING!
♪ DON'T YOU KNOW
IT'S A SCREAM? ♪
♪ LITTLE BROWN EYES,
SHE'S THE FIRST TO GO ♪
♪ IT'S A SCENE ♪
♪ THE DEVIL IS HUNGRY ♪
♪ HE'S THE STAR OF THE SHOW ♪
♪ HE'S A FIEND ♪
[MOANING]
♪ JUST A NIGHTMARE
IN A GHOST MASK ♪
♪ MYSTERY ♪
♪ THE ANSWER, MY FRIEND ♪
♪ IS BLOWING IN THE WIND ♪
YO, WHAT'S UP?
UGH!
WATCH YOUR BACK.
COMING THROUGH.
PARTY BEER.
WHAT'S UP?
[POLICE RADIO SQUAWKS]
P.A.: GOOD MORNING,
STUDENTS.
CHEERLEADER TRYOUTS
WILL BE HELD AFTER SCHOOL
TODAY IN THE GYM.
YOU MUST BE 18
AND COMFORTABLE
WITH PARTIAL NUDITY.
♪ DON'T YOU KNOW
IT'S A SCREAM? ♪
♪ LITTLE BROWN EYES,
SHE'S THE FIRST TO GO ♪
♪ IT'S A SCENE ♪
♪ IT'S A SCREAM ♪
Boy: DID NOT!
Girl: DID, TOO.
DID NOT!
DID, TOO.
DID, TOO!
MOM!
UH, WHOOPS.
ALL RIGHT, DAWSON.
IF YOU JUST SIGN HERE,
YOU'LL BE
OFFICIALLY REGISTERED
AT BULIMIA FALLS
HIGH SCHOOL.
HEY, HEY, HEY,
NEW KID.
SLAB, IS THAT THE WAY
WE INTRODUCE OURSELVES
TO THE NEW KID?
SORRY, MISS PEACOCK.
[GASPS]
HA HA!
2 FOR FLINCHIN', NEW KID.
OH! UNH!
[GROANS]
HI. I'M DAWSON.
THAT'S BETTER.
Principal: WE HAVE RULES
AT THIS SCHOOL, MISTER.
NO MEANS NO.
I'M NEVER
GONNA GET LAID.
OH, DAWSON, I'D LIKE
TO INTRODUCE YOU
TO PRINCIPAL INTEREST.
AHEM.
OH, I'M SORRY.
"THE ADMINISTRATOR FORMERLY
KNOWN AS PRINCIPAL."
[RASPBERRY BERET PLAYS]
[SIZZLE, BANG]
WANNABE.
HEY, NEW KID.
WHOA. OH, GOD!
LOOKS LIKE SOMEONE'S GONNA
HAVE TO SHOW YOU THE ROPES.
BONER!
IT'S PRONOUNCED
"BONNER," SIR.
THE "O" IS SOFT.
NOT ACCORDING
TO RESUSCI-ANNIE.
JUST SHOW HIM AROUND.
AND FOR GOD'S SAKES,
WASH YOUR HANDS FIRST.
MARY, YOU'RE NEXT.
HI. I'M BONNER.
IT'S NICE TO MEET YA.
UH-HUH.
OH, YEAH. "WITCH?"
TRY "RHYMES WITH..."
CHARMED MY ASS.
CALL ME!
DAMN SHANNEN DOHERTY.
HEY, NEW KID.
I'M BARBARA.
HOW'D YOU LIKE
A HERTZ DONUT?
I'D LOVE ONE.
THANKS.
OW!
HURTS, DON'T IT?
HA HA!
HEY, GUYS.
HEY, MARTINA.
HEY, MRS. PEACOCK.
HEY, NEW KID.
[MOANS]
[SEXY MUSIC PLAYS]
[THINKING]
WAIT A MINUTE.
IS SHE...
[BELL RINGS]
SO, DID YOU GUYS
HEAR THE NEWS?
WRESTLING IS FAKE?
I'M NOT PREGNANT?
HE WHO SMELT IT
DEALT IT?
NO. ABOUT SCREW.
SLUT.
WHORE.
DO YOU HAVE
HER NUMBER?
WHO?
SCREW FROMBEHIND.
SHE WAS KILLED,
MURDERED, GUTTED,
FLAYED, SLICED,
DICED, FRIED,
AND HUNG.
JESUS.
MM-HMM.
I'M NEVER
GONNA GET LAID.
OH, YEAH.
AND IT'S ALL OVER
THE TV AND NEWS.
OH, GREAT.
NOW EVERYBODY KNOWS.
DO THEY KNOW
WHO DID IT?
SOME GUY
IN A GHOST MASK.
THAT DOESN'T
SOUND SCARY.
STORE-BOUGHT?
EWW.
OH. OOH.
P.A.: ATTENTION, STUDENTS.
THE FIGHT BETWEEN
THE BLOODS AND THE CRIPS
IS POSTPONED
UNTIL NEXT FRIDAY.
REFRESHMENTS AND
A LOVELY DANCE WILL FOLLOW.
WELL, AT LEAST
I FEEL SAFE HERE.
HI, CHUCKY.
WANNA PLAY?
WE'LL DEFINITELY
BE OK AT SCHOOL.
YEAH. NOTHING CAN
HAPPEN TO US HERE.
[BOMB BEEPS]
[MACHINE GUN FIRE]
THIS IS THE KIND OF
THING YOU READ ABOUT.
BOOKS ARE PRETTY.
OH, MY GOD.
HE'S RIGHT.
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
KIDS GET KILLED
EVERY DAY.
THIS IS HIGH SCHOOL.
Slab: NO, DAWSON.
THIS KID WAS WHITE.
SO?
AND SHE WAS POPULAR,
LIKE ME.
OH.
I HOPE THAT'S
BARBARA WALTERS.
WHAT A RACK.
HI. I'M HAGITHA UTSLAY
FROM EMPTY-V NEWS.
KIDS, WHAT DO YOU
THINK ABOUT...
Hagitha: WAIT.
IS THAT DAWSON?
TAPE THIS.
CHOP-CHOP,
YOU FAT RAT BASTARD!
HI. I'M HAGITHA UTSLAY LIVE
FROM BULIMIA FALLS HIGH,
WHERE WE'RE SURROUNDED HERE
BY A GROUP
OF INNOCENT STUDENTS,
MOST IMPORTANTLY,
DAWSON DEERY...
STUDENT, DRUM MAJOR,
AND INSPIRATION FOR
MY BEST-SELLING BOOK:
DAWSON IS A MURDERER.
THAT BOOK SUCKED.
NOT ACCORDING TO OPRAH.
IT WAS HER
PICK OF THE MONTH.
SO WAS CHICKEN SOUP
FOR THE BUTT.
DOESN'T MEAN
I KILLED ANYONE.
NOW STAY AWAY FROM ME.
OH, COME ON, DAWSON.
ISN'T IT TRUE THAT
YOUR WHOLE ENTIRE FAMILY
WAS MURDERED UNDER
MYSTERIOUS CIRCUMSTANCES
WHILE YOU WERE
SUPPOSEDLY AT... "CAMP"?
HUH?
HUH.
UGH.
[BELL RINGS]
All: OOH!
BITCH WENT DOWN!
JUST LIKE HOME.
Boner: DAMN!
YEAH. THAT, AND THEY DIDN'T
HAVE A BOXING TEAM.
GUYS, THAT IS NO WAY
TO TREAT A LADY.
UNLESS SHE BURNS
THE TOAST.
THAT'S NO LADY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE,
ANYWAY, DOUGHY?
YOU'RE NOT A REAL COP.
SHOULDN'T YOU BE GUARDING
THE ORANGE JULIUS?
N.Y.P.D. GAP.
SERGEANT SEARS.
FOOD COURT POLICE.
HOW MANY TIMES
HAVE I TOLD YOU GUYS
MALL SECURITY
IS JUST AS IMPORTANT
AS THE REAL POLICE?
IT IS!
LOITERING AND STEALING
PENNIES FROM THE FOUNTAIN
ARE SERIOUS CRIMES
THAT CARRY...
MOM SAYS YOU'RE
A LOSER ANYWAY.
WELL, MOM SAYS
YOU GOT A FAT ASS.
DAD LEFT BECAUSE
HE HATED YOU.
NO. HE LEFT BECAUSE
WELL, HE WASN'T EVEN
YOUR REAL DAD ANYWAY.
YOU KNOW,
I READ YOUR DIARY,
MISS "BOO-HOO, MY GYM
TEACHER MOLESTED ME."
DORK.
DYKE.
WHAT?
Hagitha: EXCUSE ME.
I DON'T MEAN TO INTERRUPT
THIS FAMILY REUNION,
BUT ARE YOU ACTUALLY
WORKING ON THIS CASE,
OFFICER, UH...
UH, PRIMESSUSPEKT,
DOUGHY PRIMESSUSPEKT,
AND YES, I AM.
IT TECHNICALLY FALLS
UNDER MY JURISDICTION
BECAUSE THE KILLER'S
COSTUME WAS STOLEN
FROM THE SPENCERS
AT MY MALL.
THAT, AND, UH, YOU KNOW,
WHOOPEE CUSHIONS
AND SOME FAKE DOG SHIT.
PARDON ME... CANINE SHIT.
WHO CARES
ABOUT THAT CRAP?
I DO.
A COOL KID WAS
GUTTED LAST NIGHT.
COME ON.
IT'S PROBABLY
SOME HARMLESS
HIGH-SCHOOL PRANK.
LOOK.
THIS IS LAME.
LET'S GET
OUT OF HERE.
HEY, YOU GUYS.
I GOT AN IDEA.
LET'S ALL MAKE A PACT
TO LOSE OUR VIRGINITIES
BEFORE GRADUATION.
I'M IN.
Other kids: WE'RE NOT.
YEAH. ME, NEITHER.
Slab: YEAH!
WHOO!
YEAH.
LITTLE BASTARDS.
I COULD JUST KILL 'EM.
YEAH, BUT YOU DIDN'T,
DID YOU?
I'M JUST KIDDING YOU.
NO, REALLY.
YOU DIDN'T KILL 'EM,
DID YOU?
SO, YOU'RE ONE OF THOSE
NETWORK REPORTERS, HUH?
ACTUALLY, CABLE...
BUT IT'S
JUST AS IMPORTANT.
OH, IT'S MORE IMPORTANT.
BECAUSE ON CABLE, YOU CAN
SEE BUTTS AND BOOBIES,
AND YOU CAN SAY
"BULLSHIT" AND "BASTARD."
SO, DO YOU ACTUALLY
HAVE ANY INSIDE DIRT?
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
I DO.
[GASPS]
KILLER BOOT.
THANKS.
I LIKE YOURS, TOO.
OH, THANKS.
SO, UM, I GUESS
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
I HOPE SO.
OH. SORRY.
IT'S OK.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
COME ON, LARD ASS!
I'M GONNA
KEEP MY EYE ON HER.
SHE'S GOT CLASS.
[MAN SCREAMS]
[PULP FICTION-LIKE
MUSIC PLAYING]
P.A.: ATTENTION, STUDENTS.
THE BAND FUND-RAISER
WILL BE HELD NEXT THURSDAY
IN THE AUDITORIUM.
LIQUOR IN THE FRONT,
POKER IN THE REAR.
[SIZZLES]
[GIRL MOANS]
OH.
[AIR HISSES]
[POP]
[GIRL SCREAMS]
[SCREAM]
I DIDN'T DO IT.
WE DIDN'T SAY
YOU DID IT.
BONER, YOU COULDN'T
GET LAID AT LILITH FAIR,
MUCH LESS KILL SOMEBODY.
I COULD, TOO.
WELL, KILL SOMEBODY,
I MEAN.
I COULD KILL
ALL OF YOU.
BUT I WOULDN'T!
[SIGHS]
THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
I DIDN'T DO IT.
NOW, SLAB...
HE'S A KILLER.
JUST LOOK AT
THOSE EARLOBES...
WAY LOW.
REALLY?
OOH.
SKINNY MIRROR.
MAN, THAT GUY
LOOKS REALLY FAMILIAR.
THAT'S SPACEY,
DAWSON.
HE'S BANGING
THE FRENCH TEACHER.
REALLY?
SHE'S FROM FRANCE.
PARIS, FRANCE.
MADAME LA TOURNEAU.
[PURRS]
YEAH. HE SAYS
THE SEX IS AWESOME.
LUCKY DOG.
AU REVOIR, SPACEY.
CALL ME LATER.
SAY, "BYE-BYE, PAPA.
BYE-BYE."
[BABY CRIES]
HEY, MARTINA.
NO, BONER.
HEY, DAWSON.
DO YOU HAVE ANY LOTION
I CAN BORROW?
IT'S FOR MY RASH.
I GOT TO GO TO CLASS.
[BELL RINGS]
Teacher: OK. OK.
SETTLE DOWN, CLASS.
SETTLE DOWN. DOWN.
THAT'S IT. THAT'S IT.
I'M YOUR SUBSTITUTE...
MRS. TINGLE.
[GUNS COCK]
TODAY WE'RE
GOING TO BE STUDYING
ABOUT THE PERSECUTION
OF THE JEWISH PEOPLE.
WHO CAN TELL ME
WHAT THE VERB IS
IN THIS SENTENCE?
SABRINA? MOESHA? DARIA?
OOH, EEH? OOH, AH, AH?
Mrs. Tingle:
WHO CAN TELL ME
IF FRANKENSTEIN
WAS CIRCUMCISED?
Woman: MARTINA,
DON'T FORGET TO GIVE
GRANDMA HER LAXATIVE.
I WON'T.
[GURGLING]
SLAB, I THINK
YOU'VE HAD ENOUGH.
WHY?
BECAUSE YOU WON'T
HAVE ANY ROOM FOR BEER.
WHOA! HEY!
WHOO! THAT WAS CLOSE.
WHOO, MAN, IF I WRECKED,
MY DAD WOULD KILL ME.
HAND ME A BEER.
GUYS, OUR SENIOR YEAR
IS GONNA BE THE BEST EVER.
I'M THE NEW
KIELBASA QUEEN.
AND I JUST GOT ACCEPTED
TO HARVARD LAW SCHOOL, BABY.
I JUST GOT A FOREIGN
EXCHANGE STUDENT
LIVING IN MY HOUSE.
SHE'S SWEDISH.
AND I JUST GOT
A "D" IN MATH!
Slab and Boner: YEAH!
SLAB, LOOK OUT!
All: AAH!
[TIRES SCREECH]
I THINK I HIT SOMETHING.
OH, I THINK
I'M GONNA BE SICK.
[POP]
YEP,
I'VE GOT A FEVER.
SLAB, YOU GOT BLOOD
ALL OVER YOU.
OH,
THAT'S NO PROBLEM.
IT COMES OUT WITH
A LITTLE TEQUILA.
HA HA.
OLD SCOUT TRICK.
SLAB,
GIVE ME A HAND.
WASN'T THAT TROPHY
ENOUGH?
YES, BUT WE HAVE
TO DUMP THIS DEER.
ALL RIGHT, SWEETIE.
CAN EVERYBODY
KEEP A SECRET?
[FOGHORN]
[WOMAN GROANS]
[FARTS]
Woman: MARTINA-AAH.
[FART]
[GROANS]
[CRASH]
YES. THIS NEVER HAPPENED.
[SPLASH]
[MAN HUMMING]
Mrs. Tingle:
WHO CAN TELL ME
HOW TO CONJUGATE
THE VERB "EXPIRE"?
DOUGHY.
THAT'S AN INTERESTING NAME.
THANKS.
IT'S MY DAD'S NAME.
HE'S A BAKER.
HAGITHA...
NOW THAT'S
A BEAUTIFUL NAME.
THANKS.
MY FRIENDS CALL ME HAG.
OH, DO THEY?
THAT'S SO CUTE.
DAMN IT.
SHE'S FLAT!
ACTUALLY,
THEY'RE "C" CUPS.
I GUESS I GOT TO
GET THESE THINGS REDONE.
DOUGHY...
UH, DOUGHY,
I WAS WONDERING,
HOW DID YOU GET INTO
THIS LINE OF WORK?
WELL, I GOT TOO FAT
FOR THE BALLET,
AND I COULD NEVER
GET MY BULGE RIGHT,
YOU KNOW, SO I FIGURED
WHAT THE HELL.
[CHUCKLES]
HAGITHA...
DO YOU HAVE A BOYFRIEND?
WELL, NOT YET.
OH, MAIL ORDER, HUH?
YEAH. I'VE TRIED THAT
A FEW TIMES MYSELF.
LISTEN.
IF IT DOESN'T WORK OUT,
WOULD YOU LET ME KNOW?
I SURE WILL.
THANK YOU.
YEAH.
[TWEET]
OW!
OK. TIFFANY, AMBER,
INTO THE CHAIR.
COME ON. SHAKE IT!
MAMA.
LADIES.
NOW,
I NEED A VOLUNTEER.
BONER!
YOU LOOK LIKE A VICTIM.
YOU'RE UP.
BUT, MR. HASSELHOF,
I-I-I CAN'T SWIM.
PERFECT.
NO.
AAH!
MARCO!
OH!
I WANT TO LIVE.
OH, YEAH.
YEAH. RIGHT NOW, PLEASE.
YEAH.
NOT SO MUCH TONGUE,
AMBER.
NOW, THIS IS
A TEXTBOOK EXAMPLE
OF MOUTH-TO-MOUTH
RESUSCITATION.
SOME OF YOU MAY WANT TO
PRACTICE THIS AT HOME
OR, IF YOU'D LIKE
TO STAY AFTER CLASS,
I'D BE MORE THAN
HAPPY TO POINT OUT...
Both: EWW!
BONER!
IT'S BONNER, SIR.
NOT AT THE MOMENT.
[WHIMPERS]
YOU HAVE TO MAKE SURE
THIS GETS TO THE GOVERNOR
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
IT'S MY LAST CHANCE,
LITTLE BROTHER.
OTHERWISE, I'LL FRY.
DON'T WORRY, JIMMY.
YOU CAN COUNT ON ME.
TIME'S UP,
BONER!
IT'S BONNER, MA'AM.
NOT FOR LONG.
DEAD BONER WALKIN'!
[GATE BUZZES]
I HOPE YOU GUYS
DON'T MIND,
I MAY HAVE TO
GET HOME EARLY.
ME AND MILLIE,
MY SWEDISH EXCHANGE STUDENT,
ARE ABOUT HALFWAY
THROUGH THE KAMA SUTRA.
OH, BONNER, I DON'T
WANT TO SHARE YOU.
YEAH. WHAT'S SHE GOT
THAT WE DON'T HAVE?
A TWIN SISTER.
[GASPS]
SLAB, LOOK OUT!
AAH!
CAN EVERYBODY
KEEP A SECRET?
Jimmy's voice: I'LL FRY.
[ECHOED] FRY...
[LIGHT BUZZES]
YES.
THIS NEVER HAPPENED.
[SPLASH]
[WHIMPERS]
I'M NEVER GONNA GET LAID.
[HARD ROCK PLAYING]
[MUFFLED SCREAM]
[BEEP]
"I KAN... KANOW...
"KANOW. I K-NOW WH...
[GRUNTS]
"WH-WHAT...
"I K-NOW WHAT YEH...
"YEOW...
"I K-NOW WHAT YOU..."
Martina: SLAB, I THINK
YOU'VE HAD ENOUGH.
REALLY, DARLING?
YOUR CONCERN
IS ADMIRABLE
BUT COMPLETELY
WITHOUT MERIT.
I'M DOING
SPLENDIDLY!
ANYONE READ
THAT ARTICLE
IN THE TIMES SCIENCE
SECTION LAST WEEK?
IT SEEMS GENE SPLICING
IS ALL THE RAGE.
SLAB, LOOK OUT!
AAH!
CAN EVERYBODY
KEEP A SECRET?
UH-HUH.
Man: SLAB, I'M LOOKING
FOR YOUR UNCLE LOU'S URN.
WE'RE SCATTERING
HIS ASHES TODAY.
HAVE YOU SEEN IT?
[CHOKES]
NO!
[COUGHS]
YES.
THIS NEVER HAPPENED.
[SPLASH]
"SHAN... SHANU... CHANAK..."
[BELL RINGS]
"CHAN... CHANAKA...
CHANA... KHAN... CHACHI..."
[SHOES SQUEAK]
[SIGHS]
BARBARA,
I'M AFRAID IT'S
WORSE THAN WE FEARED.
NURSE KEVORKIAN,
YOU MEAN...?
YES, BARBARA,
YOU HAVE CHLAMYDIA
[GASPS]
AND GONORRHEA
AND SYPHILIS
[GASPS]
AND CRABS.
[BIG GASP]
WHEW. I THOUGHT YOU
WERE GONNA SAY I HAD HERPES.
OH, YES, AND HERPES.
DAMN THOSE STARBUCKS'
TOILET SEATS.
NOW, YOUNG LADY,
ISN'T THERE
SOMEBODY SPECIAL
YOU WISH TO MAKE AWARE
OF YOUR CONDITION?
YOU MEAN LIKE A TEACHER
OR MY DAD?
WELL, I WAS THINKING
MORE LIKE A BOYFRIEND.
OH. DO YOU
HAVE A YEARBOOK?
[SIGHS]
BARBARA, BARBARA,
PLEASE TAKE SOME
ADVICE FROM A WOMAN
WHO'S HAD SOME
EXPERIENCE IN THIS AREA.
I WISH TO
EXPLAIN SOMETHING
THAT WE
IN THE HEALTH PROFESSION
REFER TO AS
"HITTING SKINS."
"KNOCKING BOOTS..."
"DOING THE NASTY..."
"BUMPING UGLIES?"
I'M TALKING
ABOUT SEX, DEAR.
OH.
SEX CAN BE A BEAUTIFUL,
SENSUAL EXPERIENCE
BETWEEN A MAN
AND A WOMAN
WHO TRULY
LOVE EACH OTHER
AND WANT TO
SHARE ETERNITY
LAYING IN EACH OTHER'S
GENTLE EMBRACE...
OR IT CAN BE A DIRTY,
FILTHY SPANKFEST
IN A BUS STATION
BATHROOM
SHARED BY 2 ANONYMOUS
CONSENTING ADULTS
ON A LAYOVER IN DETROIT,
AND NOBODY
EVER NEED KNOW.
[SIGHS]
WELL, I THINK
YOU GOT MY POINT.
NOW, UH, SHOULD WE GO
AND LOOK AT YOUR X-RAYS?
X-RAYS
WITH A PAP SMEAR?
OH, WE'RE
VERY THOROUGH HERE.
I JUST CAN'T FIGURE OUT
WHAT THIS WHITE SPOT IS.
Nurse: YOU KNOW,
A PAIR OF TUBE SOCKS
WORKS EVER SO MUCH BETTER.
WHY,
WHEN I WAS YOUR AGE,
I HAD THIS EXPERIENCE
I'LL NEVER FORGET.
THERE WERE 3 OF US,
3 OF US IN ONE BED.
[NURSE KEVORKIAN LAUGHS]
[MOANS]
Woman: BARBARA, HONEY!
I'M EXPECTING
THE REVEREND JOHNSON TODAY.
DID HE COME YET?
ALMOST!
[MOANS]
BARBARA, I COULD NEVER
BE AS BEAUTIFUL AS YOU.
OR SWALLOW
AS MUCH SAUSAGE.
CAN I HAVE
YOUR AUTOGRAPH?
WILL YOU
MARRY ME?
NO. ME!
RELAX. THERE'S PLENTY
OF BARBARA TO GO AROUND.
TODAY MISS KIELBASA QUEEN.
TOMORROW THE WORLD.
CARMEN ELECTRA,
WATCH YOUR BACK.
SLAB, LOOK OUT!
All: AAH!
CAN EVERYBODY
KEEP A SECRET?
[GASPS]
YES. THIS NEVER HAPPENED.
[SPLASH]
[BELL RINGS]
...AND THAT'S HOW I KNEW
I WASN'T A LESBIAN.
NOW, BARBARA,
I THINK YOU NEED
TO TAKE THIS
SAFE-SEX KIT WITH YOU.
YOU NEVER KNOW
WHEN YOU MAY NEED IT.
I GOT TO GO.
ALL RIGHT,
BUT IT MAY NOT BE HERE
WHEN YOU COME BACK.
OH-HO.
HEY, DOUGHY.
HEY, BABY.
CHICKEN?
A LITTLE,
BUT IT'S MY JOB.
DO YOU HAVE
ANY NEW SUSPECTS YET?
WELL, WE'RE CHECKING OUT
EVERYONE IN TOWN.
ANY NEW DEVELOPMENTS?
YEAH,
MY VACATION PICTURES.
OH.
WHO'S THAT,
YOUR GRANDMOTHER?
WITH THE BONG? YEAH.
GLAUCOMA?
SPRING BREAK.
THAT'S ME.
OOH. NO TAN LINES.
I FEEL LIKE A HOT DOG.
FOOT LONG?
AT LEAST.
I'M BUYING.
WHOA!
I'VE GOT A WEIRD
FEELING, DAWSON.
WAIT TILL YOU EAT
THE TUNA TACOS.
NO. I MEAN,
SCREW BEING KILLED.
OH, THAT.
THERE'S A CRAZED KILLER
ON THE LOOSE, DAWSON.
THAT DEAD POPULAR KID
COULD'VE BEEN
ANY ONE OF US.
BUT IT WASN'T.
SO WHAT DO YOU CARE?
WHAT ABOUT NEXT TIME
HE ATTACKS?
AND YOU KNOW HE WILL.
DO YOU HAVE
A RESERVATION, SIR?
DAWSON.
PARTY OF FIVE?
WRONG NETWORK.
YES, OF COURSE,
SIR.
RIGHT THIS WAY,
I WOULDN'T WORRY ABOUT IT
SO MUCH IF I WERE YOU.
WHY?
BECAUSE
YOU'RE WITH ME.
DIDN'T YOUR WHOLE FAMILY
GET CHOPPED UP
AND FED TO A FISH FARM?
ALLEGEDLY.
AND WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
YOU'RE SO SPECIAL
HE'D WANT
TO KILL YOU, ANYWAY?
WELL,
BECAUSE I GOT THIS.
AND HOW DO YOU KNOW
IT'S A HE?
BECAUSE...
SERIAL KILLERS AND
DENTISTS ARE ALWAYS MEN.
I SAY ROOFIES
ARE BULLSHIT.
I TAKE THEM
BEFORE EVERY DATE,
AND I NEVER
GET LAID.
MAYBE YOU'RE
NOT TAKING ENOUGH.
YOU GOT ONE, TOO?
Barbara: IF THAT'S
WHAT I THINK IT IS,
I GOT ONE.
PRESCRIPTION
FOR GYNE-LOTRIMIN?
OH, WRONG PAPER.
WHAT DOES THIS MEAN?
I THINK
I GOT ONE, TOO.
WHAT DOES
YOURS SAY, SLAB?
"SHANU-SHA-SHA..."
GIVE ME THAT.
THAT'S IT.
WE'RE ALL TARGETS.
OH, GOD.
I KNEW MY BEAUTY
WOULD BE A CURSE.
THE BOTTOM LINE IS
EVERYBODY GOT A NOTE.
WE'RE ALL IN DANGER.
NOT EVERYBODY.
UNH.
FINE. HAPPY NOW?
"YOU MAY ALREADY
BE A VICTIM."
Man: BAD! BAD DEER!
BAD, BAD, BAD, BAD!
[DRY-VOMITS]
NO MORE SALT LICK.
DEERS DON'T TALK!
[GROANS]
[DOOR OPENS]
[FARTS]
Slab: WHAT'S THAT?
Martina:
SLAB, LOOK OUT!
Dawson: AAH!
NO! I JUST ATE!
[SPLASH]
All: YES.
THIS NEVER HAPPENED.
WOW!
WHAT DID YOU WIN?
DUH, EINSTEIN.
IT MEANS DAWSON'S
THE FIRST ONE ON
THE CHOPPING BLOCK.
WHAT A RELIEF.
BIG DEAL... NOTES.
IT'S PROBABLY JUST
SOME KID PLAYING A JOKE.
I MEAN, AFTER ALL,
IT IS HALLOWEEN.
AND FRIDAY THE 13th.
ON THE SAME DAY?
IMPOSSIBLE.
SLAB'S DYSLEXIC.
BESIDES, A KID
COULDN'T WRITE THAT.
AT LEAST NOT A KID
IN PUBLIC SCHOOL.
UNLESS HE WAS
JAPANESE.
BUT THEY'RE
NOT HISTORICALLY
SERIAL KILLERS.
UH-UH-UH.
WHAT ABOUT GODZILLA?
NOT TECHNICALLY
JAPANESE.
HE WAS BORN
IN INTERNATIONAL WATERS.
AHH, SO...
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
WE? NOTHING,
DIPSHIT.
AND HOW DO I KNOW
IT'S NOT ONE OF YOU GUYS?
WELL, WE COULD MAKE
HANDWRITING SAMPLES.
SLAB'S OUT.
WHOO-HOO!
NOT A KILLER!
RIGHT HERE!
WAIT A SECOND.
JUST BECAUSE
HE CAN'T READ
DOESN'T MEAN
HE'S NOT THE KILLER.
YEAH. LOOK
AT THE CLINTONS.
Others: WHAT?
NO. THIS IS STUPID,
AND YOU'RE STUPID.
WHY WOULD WE WANT
TO KILL EACH OTHER?
YEAH. SO WHAT IF SLAB
LOST MY TERM PAPER
AFTER HE COPIED IT AND
TURNED IT IN AS HIS OWN
AND GOT AN "A."
YEAH. AND SO WHAT
IF BARBARA TOLD EVERYONE
I GOT A SMALL "SHWONTZ."
EVEN THOUGH I DON'T.
EXACTLY. AND SO WHAT
IF BONER'S DAD WAS
CHEATING WITH MY MOM,
LEADING TO HER DOWNWARD
SPIRAL INTO ALCOHOLISM.
MY DAD IS WHAT?
AND YOU KNOW WHAT'S
REALLY STRANGE,
IS SOMEHOW,
THE KILLER ALWAYS
KNOWS WHERE WE ARE.
OOH. OOF.
All: YEAH.
YOU KNOW WHAT
WE'VE GOT TO DO?
WE'VE GOT TO
GET OUT OF HERE.
TO SOMEPLACE
SAFE.
YEAH, IN THE MIDDLE
OF NOWHERE...
IN THE DARK WOODS
AND POURING RAIN...
WITHOUT ANY
ADULT SUPERVISION
OR POLICE PROTECTION
ANYWHERE IN THE NEAR VICINITY.
AND I KNOW JUST THE PLACE.
IT'S TOTALLY DESERTED
EVER SINCE THOSE DORKY KIDS
WERE DISMEMBERED.
ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT BAND CAMP?
WAIT A SECOND.
THIS IS STUPID.
LET'S JUST ALL GO
TO ONE OF YOUR HOUSES.
HEY, THAT'S COOL.
MY PARENTS
ARE OUT OF TOWN.
THEY WON'T
BOTHER US.
NO.
LET'S GO TO MY HOUSE.
MY PARENTS ARE
LOCKED IN THE BASEMENT.
THEY'LL TOTALLY
LEAVE US ALONE.
Barbara:
NO, MY HOUSE.
MY PARENTS ARE DIVORCED,
AND I SPEND THE WEEKENDS
WITH MY DAD,
BUT HE TRIES TO MAKE UP
FOR LOST TIME
BY LETTING ME GET AWAY
WITH MURDER.
[ALL GASP]
WELL, YOU KNOW
WHAT I MEAN.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO TO MY HOUSE.
MY PARENTS ARE DEAD.
ALL RIGHT!
COOL.
ALL RIGHT, SO WE'LL
STAY THERE THE NIGHT,
AND WE'LL BE SAFE.
OK, SO IT'S SETTLED, THEN.
WE'LL ALL MEET UP
AT SLAB'S HOUSE.
UNTIL THEN,
WATCH YOUR BACKS.
P.A.: WILL THE FOLLOWING
STUDENTS
PLEASE REPORT
TO THE PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE.
JACK MEOFF, MIKE CUNT, LOSE HER,
AND HEYWOOD YOUBUMP.
AH, WELL, YOUR
UM, READING SCORES
ARE AVERAGE, JIMMY,
BUT, UH, BUT YOU'RE KILLING
ON A 12th-GRADE LEVEL.
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU'RE GONNA DO JUST FINE
AT THE SEMINARY.
[BELL RINGS]
[COYOTE HOWLS]
[WOMEN LAUGHING]
Woman: HOW ABOUT
THAT MICHAEL DUNNE?
NOW THERE'S AN ASS
THAT WON'T QUIT.
Second woman:
YOU'RE TELLING ME.
HE'S IN MY
THIRD PERIOD CLASS.
I'D LIKE TO JUMP
HIS BONES.
[WOMEN LAUGH]
[TOILETS FLUSH]
HEY, DID YOU FINISH
GRADING YOUR TERM PAPERS?
NO, I WAS
TOO HUNG OVER.
DID YOU READ
ANY OF YOURS?
NEVER READ THEM.
WHO DOES?
HEY, DO YOU KNOW
WHERE I CAN GET
AN UNREGISTERED
HANDGUN?
YOU GOT 50 BUCKS?
UM...
I CAN GET IT BY FRIDAY.
I'LL SEE WHAT I CAN DO.
[SUBMARINE RADAR PINGING]
[DEEP BREATH]
[SCREAMS]
♪ DO, DO, DO, DO, DO, DO ♪
♪ DO WAAA ♪
♪ YOU'RE NEVER FRESH
OUT OF TUNE ♪
♪ WHEN YOU'RE HOLDING
THE KNIFE ♪
♪ WITH MENTALS THIS
WILL BE YOUR NIGHT ♪
♪ LADY LUCK WILL
LIFT YOU UP ♪
♪ WHEN YOU'RE SPORTING
FRESH BREATH ♪
♪ BEFORE YOU STRIKE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOUR DEATH GOES
BETTER WITH MENTALS FRESHNESS ♪
♪ DEATH GOES BETTER
WITH MENTALS FRESHNESS ♪
WITH YOU ♪
♪ WHAT ARE YOU
DOING TONIGHT? ♪
JEEZ.
P.A.: ATTENTION, STUDENTS.
TONIGHT'S P.T.A. MEETING
WILL BE HELD AT
THE HOOTERS RESTAURANT
IN GLENDALE.
PLEASE REMIND
YOUR PARENTS.
ALSO, WHOEVER PUT REAL MEAT
IN TODAY'S LUNCH,
PLEASE REMOVE IT.
MAN, THIS CAR SUCKS.
WHAT A PIECE OF SHIT.
[SNORTS, SPITS]
HEY, GUYS, WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
DON'T YOU SEE
WHAT I SEE?
WHY, THIS CAR'S
AUTOMATIC.
SYSTEMATIC.
IT'S HYDROMATIC.
WHY, IT'S GREASE FRIGHTNING.
[1950's MUSIC PLAYING]
WHAT A FAG.
LET'S GO PIN IT
ON HIS LOCKER. FAG.
OF COURSE IT'S STUPID
IF NO ONE ELSE SINGS.
DICKS.
WHATEVER.
[LONG SIGH]
HUH.
HUH? MR. ANDRETTI?
[MOTOR RUMBLES]
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYS]
AAAAAAAAHHHH!
AAAAAAHHH!
[POLICE SIREN BLARES]
GREAT.
MOTHER-SCRATCHER.
[SIGHS]
LICENSE AND
ACTIVE WARRANTS?
[HORN BLARES]
P.A.: MAY I HAVE
YOUR ATTENTION
FOR THE RESULTS OF
YESTERDAY'S PREGNANCY TESTS.
SUSAN SAVINSKY, NEGATIVE.
MELISSA BLAKE, POSITIVE.
JONATHAN WINER, NEGATIVE.
DID YOU KNOW THAT
MOST SERIAL KILLERS
HAVE AN EXTRA
CHROMOSOME?
OH, REALLY?
YEAH, TRUST ME.
I'M FROM WISCONSIN.
THAT'S
A REALLY NICE GUN.
THANKS. MY MOM
BOUGHT IT FOR ME.
NOW I'M SAVING UP
FOR BULLETS.
HMM. 9 MILLIMETER?
WHEN IT'S COLD.
YOU KNOW A LOT
ABOUT THIS STUFF.
WELL, I HAVE TO.
MY DEMO SHOWED THAT
I'M MOST POPULAR
WITH FELONS
AND BEDWETTERS.
HMM. PERFECT.
THEN, I'M YOUR MAN.
YOU DO
LIKE TO WATCH.
[CAMERAMAN
STILL GAGGING]
WHO DOESN'T?
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
[BELL RINGS]
SEIG HEIL! SEIG HEIL!
SEIG HEIL!
P.A.: ATTENTION, STUDENTS.
FLIGHT 916 FOR TUSCANY
WILL BE BOARDING
AT GATE 14A.
THE WHITE ZONE
IS FOR LOADING
AND UNLOADING
OF PASSENGERS ONLY.
NO PARKING.
ALSO, TODAY'S HAPPY HOUR
WILL BE HELD
IN THE BIOLOGY LAB.
REMEMBER, WINGS ARE FREE
WHEN YOU BUY A PITCHER.
♪ SHE'S GONNA TAKE ♪
♪ THE BLINK OF AN EYE ♪
♪ I DON'T WANNA
SOUND DEFEATING ♪
♪ BUT YOU KNOW THAT SHE'S
EVERYTHING TO ME ♪
♪ SHE'S EVERYTHING ♪
♪ SHE'S GOIN' OUT ♪
♪ SHE'S GOIN' TO DO MY THING ♪
♪ WE TALK ABOUT THIS ♪
♪ SHE MAKES IT OK ♪
♪ WE GO FOR OUR... ♪
[HORN BLARES]
[CHEERING]
P.A.: WE'RE IN
THE FINAL TURN.
IT'S MARTINA
AND THE KILLER.
THE KILLER
MAKING HIS MOVE.
NOW IT'S THE KILLER
AND MARTINA.
MARTINA NOW MAKING
HER MOVE.
NOW IT'S MARTINA
AND THE KILLER.
[CHARIOTS OF FIRE-LIKE THEME
PLAYING]
THE KILLER WITH
THE FACE GEAR!
YEAH!
[BAND PLAYS]
YEAH, YEAH!
YEAH! HEY...
P.A.: ATTENTION, STUDENTS.
THERE WILL BE A FIRE DRILL
AT 3:05 TODAY.
PLEASE BRING YOUR OWN MATCHES
AND LIGHTER FLUID.
[SQUEAKING]
YAAH!
OH.
2 MINUTES TO SHOWTIME...
OR SHOULD
I SAY SHOWER TIME?
OH, YEAH.
COME TO PAPA.
[RUMBLING]
SLAB? DAWSON?
MARTINA?
EUREKA.
ALL RIGHT.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT THE?
[BELL RINGS]
OK, OK, OK.
FACULTY COMING THROUGH.
HELLO? HELLO? CHRIST.
AREN'T ANY OF YOU
ON THE INTERNET?
PUT A LEASH ON IT,
TARZAN.
HELLO, GANG.
WELCOME TO SEX EDUCATION.
IF YOU AREN'T REGISTERED
FOR THIS COURSE
OR ARE A SOUTHERN BAPTIST,
YOU'RE IN THE WRONG ROOM.
TA-TA.
A-CHURCHING WE GO.
OK, LET'S GET STARTED
BY REVIEWING THE BASICS,
SHALL WE?
WHO REMEMBERS
MY 2 FRIENDS
PETER LONGFELLOW
AND VIRGINIA TULIPS?
[SNIFFS, HUSKY VOICE]
OH, BABY.
YOU SMELL LIKE BEER.
[FEMININE VOICE]
OH, OH, PEYTON PLACE,
I'VE ALWAYS RELIED ON
THE KINDNESS OF STRANGERS.
[HUSKY VOICE]
EAT MY STRANGER.
[FEMININE VOICE]
OW! OW! DADDY, DADDY!
[HUSKY VOICE]
UGH! AH!
I'M GONNA GET IT!
[LAMAZE BREATHING]
[FEMININE VOICE]
OW! OW!
YES?
MR. BUCHANAN,
MAY I PLEASE
BE EXCUSED?
COULDN'T WAIT TILL PROM,
MS. DELGADO?
GO. GO, GO, GO, GO, GO.
ALL RIGHT. LET'S MOVE ON
TO OUR FILM, SHALL WE?
I JUST NEED A VOLUNTEER
TO PUT SOME FUELER
IN THE PROJECTOR.
ANYONE.
FUELER.
YES.
I'LL DO IT.
SUGAR BOOGER.
HERE YOU GO.
KNOCK YOURSELF OUT.
THERE YOU GO, KILLER.
YOU WON'T HAVE ANY TROUBLE
WITH THOSE DELTOIDS. HA.
ALL RIGHT,
UM, WHERE WAS I?
UH...
Announcer: THE FOLLOWING
MOTION PICTURE
HAS BEEN RATED X.
IT CONTAINS
ADULT SITUATIONS,
ADULT LANGUAGE,
AND NUDITY.
LOTS OF NUDITY.
EXTENSIVE PAUSING
OR REWINDING
WILL DAMAGE FILM.
PARENTAL ABSENCE
IS SUGGESTED.
Second announcer:
AND NOW,
FOR OUR FEATURE
PRESENTATION.
HOLOMARK HALL OF FAME
PROUDLY PRESENTS...
MOTLEY SCREW:
THE PAM AND TOMMY STORY.
Tommy: LOOK,
I'M DRIVING THE BOAT.
LOOK, I'M MEASURING
THE COUCH.
Pam: YOU LOOK LIKE
A TRIPOD.
OH. WILL YOU LOOK
AT THAT CHOICE OF WALLPAPER?
WHO IS YOUR DECORATOR?
MUSSOLINI?
Pam: MMM...
HEY, NO ONE'S
GONNA SEE THIS,
RIGHT, BABY?
Tommy: OH...
[ORGAN MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPS]
[SIGHS]
DO YOU MIND PRACTICING
SOMEWHERE ELSE?
Tommy: OH, YEAH.
OH, YEAH.
Pam: OW! OW!
HEY, THIS ISN'T GONNA
HELP MY SORE THROAT ANY,
IS IT? OW! OH, OH!
[ORGAN MUSIC PLAYING]
HA HA HA.
SCISSORS CUT PAPER.
YOU LOSE.
Tommy: HEY, LOOK.
I'M POLE-VAULTING.
Principal: AHA. THAT'S WHY
I DON'T WEAR UNDERWEAR.
MMM. THAT WAS AMAZING,
WASN'T IT, BABY?
I JUST LOVE PLAYING
NAUGHTY KILLER
AND PRISON PSYCHIATRIST
WITH YOU.
[MEOWS]
BUT NEXT TIME,
DON'T PULL IT SO TIGHT.
THAT'S MY GOOD SCARF.
HA HA HA.
LET'S SEE WHAT THE KIDS
IS UP TO.
THAT'S WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
OH, I'M SORRY, LOVER.
DID I LEAVE YOU HANGING?
I KNOW WHAT WE NEED.
♪ MARGARITAS ♪
THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
SEE? IT'S ME AND YOU, GIRL.
ALL RIGHT.
ME AND YOU.
HEY, YOU KIDS,
KNOCK OFF THE GRAB-ASS!
IT'S A GOOD THING
PRINCIPAL WINKLER
LEFT THAT FUTON BEHIND.
COME ON. I WANT
TO SHOW YOU A TRICK.
HEY! WHAT DID I
JUST TELL YOU?
LET'S GO, MAN.
I... I DIDN'T SEE YOU
COME IN.
WELL, WHAT DO
WE HAVE HERE?
UH, I WAS JUST BONING UP
ON MY... ON MY C.P.R.,
A-A-AND I GOT A SORE HIP,
SO WE WAS IN...
WHAT THE?
HEY, DON'T MAKE ME
COME DOWN THERE.
HEY. ALL RIGHT.
HA-YA!
ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S IT. UGH.
DAMN. WANNABE.
CHERRY VAN, MAN.
THANKS. I BOUGHT IT
FROM JEWEL.
IT STILL SMELLS
LIKE PEANUT BUTTER.
YEAH.
OH, MY GOD.
WE SAW HIM.
WE ALL DID.
DAWSON'S BEING INTERVIEWED
BY THE COPS RIGHT NOW.
YEAH, BUT WORKING
WITH WILLIAM KEVINSON
WAS A REALLY GREAT
EXPERIENCE FOR ME.
YOU KNOW,
HE'S A BRILLIANT GUY.
GOT IT?
YOU'RE A VERY
ATTRACTIVE MAN.
NOW, SCRAM!
I WANT
TO TAKE THAT HOME.
♪ SCHOOL'S OUT FOR SUMMER ♪
Director: 2... 1... AND...
WELCOME BACK
TO BULIMIA FALLS HIGH,
HOME OF EMPTY-V'S
SPRING BREAK MASSACRE,
WHERE WE HAVE LIVE COVERAGE
OF THE COOLEST MURDERS
IN THE COUNTRY
AND HOT NEW VIDEOS FROM
THE BACKSTREET BOYS.
SO, DOUGHY.
HEY, BABY.
UM, OFFICER PRIMESSUSPEKT?
IS IT TRUE THAT
ALL THE STUDENTS
GOT NOTES
FROM THE KILLER?
UH-HUH.
WELL, WHAT DOES IT MEAN?
ARE THEY IN DANGER?
WELL, I DON'T WANT
TO SCARE ANYBODY,
BUT I'D SAY THEY'RE ALL
STRONG CANDIDATES
FOR A GOOD,
OLD-FASHIONED
AX IN THE HEAD.
ARE WE ON LIVE?
HEY, DICKHEAD.
SHOT OF THEM! SHOT OF THEM!
[YELLING, CHEERING]
OK, OFFICER PRIMESSUSPEKT,
ARE YOU TAKING
ANY EXTRA PRECAUTIONS?
WELL, I'M WEARING
2 PAIRS OF UNDERPANTS.
DON'T TOUCH ME!
AND ALSO,
WE SENT A UNIT OUT
TO WHATEVER
DESERTED LOCATION
THESE KIDS
ARE GOING OUT TO.
WHERE IS THAT PLACE,
KIDS?
WHOO!
ROCK 'N' ROLL!
[MUSIC PLAYING,
PEOPLE TALKING]
Slab: HAS ANYBODY
SEEN MY CATS?
HEY. HEY, GIRLFRIEND.
COME ON UP HERE.
HEY, HEY. WATCH
THAT CEILING FAN.
OH.
[WET THUD,
MUSIC STOPS]
[MUSIC, TALKING RESUME]
SO I GRABBED THE BASTARD
BY HIS CHEAP COSTUME,
AND I THREW HIM
UP AGAINST THE WALL,
AND I SAID TO HIM,
"YOU WANT THE TRUTH?"
AHH. "YOU CAN'T HANDLE
THE TRUTH."
[VOMITS]
SO, DO YOU WANT
TO GO UPSTAIRS?
HA. HEY, DOUGHY.
HEY, BABY.
SO, YOU ALL READY
FOR TONIGHT?
LET'S JUST SAY I GOT
AN ITCHY TRIGGER FINGER.
POISON IVY?
NO, I SHOWERED
AT THE "Y."
OH. BAD SOAP?
YEAH. I GUESS IT'S ONLY
SUPPOSED TO BE USED
EXTERNALLY.
SO, HOW COME YOU HAVE
A RASH ON YOUR FINGER, THEN?
WELL, I HAD
TO GET IT OUT.
SO, UH, YOU THINK
THE KILLER'S GONNA SHOW UP?
IT'S HALLOWEEN,
ISN'T IT?
[LAUGHS]
[TAPPING]
COLLECTING FOR THE UNLUCKY
FISHERMAN'S ASSOCIATION.
OH, SORRY, DUDE.
I... I GAVE AT THE PIER.
OK, SO, WHAT DO YOU GUYS
WANT TO WATCH?
OH, HOW ABOUT
TELETUBBIES?
NAH. WE DON'T HAVE ANY POT.
ALL RIGHT.
WE'VE GOT HOT SHOTS,
THE NAKED GUN,
OOH, AIRPLANE.
YEAH. I HEAR IF YOU
PAUSE IT JUST RIGHT,
YOU CAN SEE
LESLIE NEILSEN'S PENIS.
All: EWW!
PARODIES ARE LAME.
I'M GONNA GET
SOME MORE BEER.
I'LL BE BACK.
WHAT ARE YOU,
CRAZY?
YOU CAN'T TALK
LIKE THAT, BARBARA.
I MEAN, WE ARE IN
A PARODY SITUATION.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
A PARODY. A KILLER IN
A "THE KILLER" COSTUME
SLAUGHTERING
A BUNCH OF GOOD-LOOKING,
HORNY STUDENTS AT, LIKE,
A RIDICULOUSLY NAMED
HIGH SCHOOL.
OK, HAS ANYBODY
SEEN SCREAM?
YEAH. GREAT FLICK.
OK, FOR CHRIST'S
SAKES, GUYS,
EMPTY V? THAT'S
LIKE THE WORST PUN
I EVER HEARD.
IT'S SO EASY.
I MEAN, HELLO?
WE ALL GOT NOTES.
I KNOW WHAT YOU DID
LAST SUMMER?
OH, OH. THAT'S NOT
WHAT MINE SAID.
CHAN-HAN. CHAN...
GIVE ME THAT.
GOD, I HAVEN'T BEEN
THIS SCARED
SINCE I TRIED OUT
FOR THE WNBA.
WHATEVER.
I'M NOT SCARED.
[CAT MEOWS]
OH, CHEAPSHOT.
THERE YOU ARE.
[MEOWS]
NOW I REALLY
NEED MORE BEER.
I MEAN, COME ON, GUYS.
LOOK AROUND YOU.
I MEAN, DAWSON.
WHAT? IT'S A FAMILY NAME.
ARE WE GONNA
BE TESTED ON THIS?
[BELL RINGS]
24-HOUR PIZZA.
IF WE'RE NOT HERE IN 24 HOURS,
WE'RE NOT COMING.
WHO ORDERED THE LARGE?
I GOT IT.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
I GOT THAT. ALLOW ME.
NO, REALLY. I GOT IT.
NO, I GOT IT.
I GOT IT.
HAGITHA, ALLOW ME.
I'LL FLIP YOU.
YOU'RE ON.
OOH!
OH!
BEST 2 OUT OF 3?
OK.
JEEZ.
ALL RIGHT, LISTEN.
THERE ARE CERTAIN RULES
YOU HAVE TO FOLLOW
IN A PARODY SITUATION
IF YOU WANT TO SURVIVE, OK?
NUMBER ONE:
EXAGGERATE EVERYTHING.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC NOTE PLAYS]
NUMBER 88: ACCEPT
THE RIDICULOUS AS LOGICAL.
DON'T WORRY. I KNOW
HOW TO PLEASE A WOMAN.
SEXUAL SIGHT GAGS,
ALWAYS FUNNY.
WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
ALMOST THERE.
COME ON, BABY, YEAH!
YEAH! YES!
YES! I GOT IT!
OH, YEAH. OH.
AND ALONG WITH
WACKY SOUND EFFECTS...
HERE'S BONER.
[UNZIPS ZIPPER]
[BOING]
AND UNLIMITED ABSURDITY.
AAH!
REMEMBER.
NOTHING IS SACRED.
DAMN IT!
PERFECT.
JUST PERFECT.
YOU'RE FORGETTING.
POINT OUT THE OBVIOUS.
MM-HMM.
AND FINALLY, PERPETUATE
PAINFUL STEREOTYPES.
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
SEE, NOW THAT'S ORION...
AND THAT'S HIS PENIS.
NO, THAT'S
THE BIG DIPPER.
REALLY? I CALL MINE
"THOR'S HAMMER."
[GASPS]
I CAN'T SEE SHIT.
OOF!
THE BOTTOM LINE IS,
PARODIES COME FROM TRUTH.
IT'S OBSERVATIONAL,
SO IF SOMETHING
LOOKS FAMILIAR, HEADS UP.
HUH?
[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
[ELECTRIC KNIFE WHIRS]
HA HA, BONER.
[ELECTRIC KNIFE
WHIRS LOUDLY]
BONER?
[LAUGHS]
[GASPS]
YEAH.
STAY BACK, ASSHOLE.
[GRUNTING]
[LAUGHS]
[DOORBELL RINGS]
YEAH.
♪ WE'VE GOT A RIGHT TO BE LOVERS ♪
♪ OOH, WE WERE MADE
FOR EACH OTH... ♪
YEAH.
YEAH!
[SCREAMS]
[LAUGHS]
HELP!
[DUELING BANJO MUSIC PLAYS]
[SCREAMS]
[LAUGHS]
DAMN THESE FAKE TITS.
Killer: OH, NO.
OHH.
WELL, THIS SURVEILLANCE WORK
IS REALLY INTERESTING.
YEAH.
MUST BE REALLY HARD
TRYING TO BE SO
INCONSPICUOUS AND QUIET.
RIGHT, WELL,
NOT EVERYBODY'S
CUT OUT FOR IT,
YOU KNOW.
HEY, HAVE YOU EVER
HEARD ME PLAY THE DRUMS?
COME HERE!
[SCREAMING]
AAH!
[LAUGHS]
[BEES BUZZING]
[WHIMPERS]
Killer: OH, DAMN.
WHOO!
HEY, NOT BAD.
ALL RIGHT,
HERE IT COMES.
All: AND DON'T
CALL ME SHIRLEY!
WHOO!
HEY, HEY, GUYS.
THEY JUST FOUND
THE ADMINISTRATOR
FORMERLY KNOWN AS PRINCIPAL
BOUND AND GAGGED. DEAD.
[GASPS]
LET'S GET DOWN THERE
BEFORE THE CORONER DOES
AND PLAY WEEKEND
AT BERNIE'S WITH HIM.
[CHEERING]
AND I NEVER GOT
A CHANCE TO KNOW HIM.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
UM, I'LL GET IT.
IT COULD BE MY ACCOUNTANT.
[RING]
WHAT?
SO, HERE WE ARE,
ALL ALONE.
RIGHT.
I HAVE SOMETHING
FOR YOU, DAWSON.
OH, YEAH?
I WANT YOU, DAWSON.
YOU WANT ME
TO WEAR THAT?
NO. THIS IS FOR ME,
BUT THIS...
IS FOR YOU.
OH.
WAIT... WAIT...
WAIT A SECOND.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
A LESBIAN?
WHY?
HELLO.
YOU PLAY SOFTBALL.
YOU WATCH ALLY McBEAL.
THE WNBA.
NO, DAWSON,
I'M NOT GAY.
BARBARA'S GAY.
BARBARA?
BIG ROSIE FAN.
BUT... BUT YOU ARE
A WITCH, RIGHT?
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
[CRASH]
WHOA!
[MEOW]
LAMEGAG, YOU SCARED
THE CRAP OUT OF US.
[MEOW]
WHAT IS IT, BOY?
[GROWLING]
I'M SORRY.
WHAT IS IT, GIRL?
[MEOW]
SLAB'S IN TROUBLE?
STEROIDS?
IN THE BATHROOM?
BURT REYNOLDS
WEARS A RUG?
[MEOW]
O.J. WAS FRAMED?
KHAKIS AREN'T COOL?
NO, I HAVE
TO DISAGREE WITH YOU.
I THINK YOU'RE COMPLETELY...
WELL, FUCK YOU, TOO!
[MEOW]
COME ON. LET'S GO.
SLAB!
OH, MY GOD.
I... I THINK I USED
TOO MUCH.
[MUSIC FROM PSYCHO PLAYS]
OH.
OH, THIS IS HORRIBLE.
I KNOW.
WHO IS GONNA
CLEAN ALL THIS UP?
[MEOW]
DAWSON, NO!
THERE'S NO POINT
IN BEATING DEAD HORSE.
[RUSTLING SOUNDS]
OK...
DAWSON, I'M GOING TO...
DAWSON?
DAWSON!
I WAS JUST
CHECKING FOR CLUES.
COULD YOU...
MMM, BEEFY!
YOU'RE TOO LATE.
♪ CAROLINE LAUGHS,
AND IT'S RAINING ALL DAY ♪
♪ SHE LOVES TO BE
ONE OF THE GIRLS ♪
♪ LIVES IN THE PLACE
INSIDE OF OUR LIVES ♪
♪ WHERE NOTHING
IS EVER PUT STRAIGHT ♪
♪ SHE TURNS HERSELF AROUND,
AND SHE SAYS ♪
♪ "THIS IS IT,
THAT'S THE END OF THE JOKE," ♪
♪ LOSES HERSELF
IN HER DREAMING AND SLEEP ♪
♪ AND HER LOVERS WALK THROUGH
IN THEIR COATS ♪
♪ SHE'S ♪
♪ PRETTY IN PINK ♪
♪ ISN'T SHE ♪
♪ PRETTY IN PINK? ♪
♪ ISN'T SHE? ♪
♪ ALL OF HER LOVERS
ALL TALK OF HER NOTES ♪
♪ AND THE FLOWERS
THAT THEY NEVER SENT ♪
♪ AND WASN'T SHE EASY? ♪
♪ ISN'T SHE
PRETTY IN PINK? ♪
♪ THE ONE WHO INSISTS
HE WAS FIRST IN THE LINE ♪
♪ IS THE LAST
TO REMEMBER HER NAME... ♪
WHOA!
[CLOTH RIPS]
♪ SHE'S GONE,
BUT THE JOKE'S THE SAME ♪
♪ PRETTY IN PINK ♪
♪ ISN'T HE? ♪
♪ CAROLINE TALKS
TO YOU SOFTLY SOMETIMES ♪
♪ SHE SAYS "I LOVE YOU"
AND "TOO MUCH" ♪
♪ SHE DOESN'T HAVE ANYTHING
YOU WANT TO STEAL ♪
♪ WELL, NOTHING
YOU CAN TOUCH ♪
♪ SHE WAVES ♪
♪ SHE BUTTONS YOUR SHIRT ♪
♪ THE TRAFFIC IS WAITING OUTSIDE ♪
♪ SHE HANDS YOU THIS COAT ♪
♪ SHE GIVES YOU HER CLOTHES,
THE CARS COLLIDE ♪
[APPLAUSE]
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, PEPPERONI BOY,
LET'S SEE 'EM.
WE MADE IT.
OH!
[MUSIC FROM PSYCHO PLAYS]
NO, HOLD ON.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF THIS.
YOU MEAN, BIG BULLY.
BAD, BAD, BAD KILLER.
I'M GONNA
SCRATCH YOUR EYES OUT,
YOU BAD BULLY...
OH, BOY!
WHOA.
HAHH!
[CLANG]
[CLANK CLANK CLANK]
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT! YEAH!
KICK HIS ASS!
OH!
JERRY! JERRY!
ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE NOT A LESBIAN?
WELL, ONCE AT CAMP.
COOL.
LET'S FIND OUT
WHO THIS ASSHOLE IS.
[GASPS]
WHO IS THAT?
ABE LINCOLN.
OHH. ABE!
OK, COME ON, NOW.
TAKE 'EM OFF.
BUT THEY'RE
COMPANY PROPERTY.
NICE.
[GASPS]
SHH. DID YOU
HEAR THAT?
OH, EXCUSE ME.
NO, NOT THAT.
[GASPS]
LET'S ROLL.
HEY, WIDELOAD,
YOU AND PIZZA DORK
GOTTA HOOF IT.
GET OFF!
WE'RE GOING IN.
COME ON.
HEY, I THINK
THIS IS THE LAST ONE.
HUH? YOU!
WHO WERE YOU EXPECTING,
BILLY LOOMIS' MOTHER?
OF COURSE.
RULE NUMBER 101,
YOU CAN'T HAVE
A SUCCESSFUL PARODY
WITHOUT MOCKING
CONTRIVED,
CONFUSING ENDINGS.
BUT WHY, DOUGHY?
I'M NOT DOUGHY,
DUMB-ASS.
OK, THAT'S
NOT EVEN REAL.
BUT IT IS DASTARDLY.
SO IF YOU'RE
NOT DOUGHY,
THAT MAKES YOU...
YES.
DOUGHY'S EVIL TWIN,
COUSIN HARDING.
WOW, GOOD TWIST.
SO WHAT'S YOUR MOTIVE?
IN THE MILLENNIUM,
MOTIVES ARE ACCIDENTAL.
UM, DO YOU MEAN
INCIDENTAL?
I SHOULD HAVE
KILLED YOU FIRST.
HEY... DON'T... HEY... NOW!
SO I SUPPOSE THIS
IS WHAT YOU USE
TO DISGUISE YOUR VOICE?
HELLO, SYDNEY!
NO, I MEAN THIS.
[KILLER VOICE]
HELLO, MARTINA.
WHAT'S YOUR
FAVORITE MOVIE?
I AM YOUR FATHER, LUKE.
FREEZE!
DON'T SHOOT.
I GIVE UP.
HARDING?
YO, DOUGH.
DOUGHY, WHAT'S...
WHAT'S GOING ON?
THEY'RE IDENTICAL.
YEAH, ONE GOOD,
ONE EVIL.
WOW.
JUST LIKE
THE OLSENS, HUH?
EXCEPT WHERE AS HARDING
ENJOYS A MINUET,
THE BALLET RUSSES
AND CREPE SUZETTE...
DOUGHY LIKES
TO ROCK AND ROLL.
A HOT DOG MAKES HIM
LOSE CONTROL.
WHAT A WILD DUET.
STILL THEY'RE COUSINS...
IDENTICAL COUSINS.
THEY LAUGH ALIKE.
THEY WALK ALIKE.
AT TIMES THEY EVEN
TALK ALIKE.
AND YOU COULD
LOSE YOUR MIND.
SHUT UP, EVERYBODY!
FOR GOD'S SAKES,
HOW MANY TIMES
DO YOU THINK WE'VE HEARD
THAT IN OUR LIVES, HUH?
A LITTLE RESPECT!
HARDING! YOU'RE A DISGRACE
AND AN EMBARRASSMENT
TO OUR FAMILY.
BECAUSE OF THE STAIN
ON GRANDMA'S DRESS?
NO.
OH, THAT. YEAH.
LISTEN, UM...
I'M REALLY SORRY.
IS THERE ANY WAY I CAN
MAKE IT UP TO YOU, DOUGHY?
WELL, FIRST OF ALL,
YOU CAN TAKE
THAT COSTUME BACK
TO ITS RIGHTFUL OWNERS
AT THE MALL.
I... I DON'T HAVE
THE RECEIPT.
I'LL MAKE SOME CALLS,
BUT DON'T FORGET ABOUT
THAT FAKE DOG SHIT.
I DIDN'T
TAKE ANY DOG SHIT.
HUH?
HMM.
ALL RIGHT,
YOU KNUCKLEHEAD,
GIVE ME A HUG.
[GUNSHOT]
OW.
NICE SHOT.
HUH?
OOH!
[MOANING]
OOPS!
YOU GUYS ALL SAW THAT.
I MEAN, THAT WAS
JUST AN ACCIDENT.
YEAH, YEAH, IT HAPPENS.
UGH,
I REALLY NEED
TO GET A NEW SHADE.
HERE, TRY MINE.
OH!
PERFECT.
WELL,
I'VE GOT MY SCOOP.
SEE YOU, DOUGHY.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT ABOUT DINNER
AT THE WIENER PUP?
OR MAYBE A SNACK
AT THE PRETZEL SHACK?
DID YOU BRING YOUR BIKE?
MM-HMM.
OK.
WHAT ABOUT US?!
PIZZA GUYS
GET ALL THE PUSSY.
DON'T WORRY, DOUGHY.
WE GOT IT ALL
UNDER CONTROL.
YEAH, EXCEPT FOR
ALL THOSE DEAD PEOPLE.
[SIRENS GROWING LOUDER]
YEAH, WELL...
LET'S GO, KIDS.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
BAG 'EM. TAG 'EM.
WE'LL WRAP THIS UP.
WE'LL TAKE IT
FROM HERE.
GET IN THERE.
COVER ME.
ALL RIGHT.
I'VE GOT YOUR BACK.
HERE WE GO.
HEY, NICE BUNS.
WHOA!
WOW, DOUGHY,
TWIN COUSINS.
YEAH, THE RESEMBLANCE
WAS REMARKABLE.
I KNOW. PEOPLE SAY
WE LOOK LIKE TOM CRUISE.
HEY, CATERING.
MARTINA. DAWSON.
BONER, YOU'RE ALIVE!
GOD BLESS VIAGRA.
IT SAVED MY LIFE.
I ATE A WHOLE BOTTLE,
AND WHEN I HAD
MY HEART ATTACK,
THE BLOOD KEPT
PUMPING ANYWAY.
I CAN TAKE THIS
FROM HERE.
YES!
WE ARE SO LUCKY
WE SURVIVED.
NOW WE CAN
BE TOGETHER FOREVER.
WELL, AT LEAST
UNTIL THE SEQUEL.
AREN'T YOU GAY?
COFFEE!
NOT ON MY WATCH, PUNK.
WELL, THAT ABOUT DOES IT.
I KILLED MY COUSIN...
MY HEART'S BROKEN...
MY SISTER'S DEAD.
DAMN IT, I LOVE THIS JOB.
OH, WELL, NOW
WE'RE SAFE, THANK GOD.
YEAH.
DO YOU WANT TO GO FOR A WALK
IN THE DARK, SCARY WOODS?
SURE.
HEY, DAWSON!
EVERYBODY, I DID IT!
I'M NOT A VIRGIN
ANYMORE!
[SIREN]
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
[RING]
Killer:
HELLO, SYDNEY.
WHAT?
I SAID...
I'M SORRY,
I'M LOSING YOU.
I SAID, HELLO, SYDNEY.
YOU'RE BREAKING UP.
HELLO?
WHO WAS IT?
I DON'T KNOW,
BUT IF IT'S IMPORTANT,
THEY'LL CALL BACK.
DARN CELL PHONES!
RICH, KNOW-IT-ALL TEENAGERS.
I'VE BEEN UP ALL NIGHT,
MY BACK HURTS,
AND I'VE GOT TO PEE.
[IT'S A SCREAM PLAYS]